hostdatsite.com 2013-04-13

# Privacy Policy | MLM Blog Expert | MLM Leads | Network Marketing Expert | Internet Marketing Expert

**Y our Business Reality Ltd**

 ****

**WEB SITE PRIVACY POLICY**

Your Business Reality Ltd,  
(referred to in this document as “COMPANY” or “We”), is concerned  
that its reputation, and the responsibilities that come with using  
it, always remain of paramount importance in all of Your Business Reality Ltd’s  
activities. To that end, in addition to certain conditions and  
restrictions that you will find under the Terms of Use Agreement  
[insert hyperlink here] and our Legal Disclaimer [insert hyperlink  
here] on our Internet Web Site, the information and links to other  
web sites provided below explain Your Business Reality Ltd’s policy about privacy,  
options you can use to limit the use of information about you both  
here and elsewhere on the internet, valuable information about the  
internet generally, public policy issues about the internet and  
internet privacy as well as other information about rights and  
responsibilities concerning privacy in a variety of non-internet  
areas.

We believe your business is no one else’s. Your privacy is important  
to you and to us. So we’ll protect the information you share with  
us. To protect your privacy, Your Business Reality Ltd follows standard principles  
in accordance with worldwide practices for Customer/Member privacy  
and data protection.

**PRIVACY POLICY**

Your Business Reality Ltd’s policy is to respect the privacy of all of our  
visitors, so the following policy statement tells you about what  
information we may receive, send or ask of you, what its used for  
and ways you can control its use.

Generally, anyone can  
come to visit hostdatsite.com, and Your Business Reality Ltd will not keep information  
about these visits except for a record of how many total visits have  
been made to the Web Site and its various web pages altogether (not  
how many times any single person has visited).

However, if you become a Customer/Member (see our Terms of Use  
Agreement [insert hyperlink here] for a detailed explanation), which  
requires giving identifying information to Your Business Reality Ltd (together  
referred to in this document as a “Customer/Member “), Membership  
records will be started according to information you give us or that  
we receive from or send to your computer.

**SECURITY**

Your Business Reality Ltd has taken strong measures to protect the security of  
your personal information and to ensure that your choices for its  
intended use are honoured. We take strong precautions to protect  
your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure,  
alteration, or destruction. Your Personal Information is stored on  
secure servers that are not accessible by third parties. We provide  
you with the capability to transmit you Personal Information via  
secured and encrypted channels if you use a similarly equipped web  
browser.

These security  
measures are in place to prevent the loss, misuse, and alteration of  
the information that we obtain from you, but we make no assurances  
about our ability to prevent any such loss, misuse, to you or to any  
third party arising out of any such loss, misuse, or alteration.

In the event of unauthorized use of your credit card, you must  
notify your credit card provider in accordance with its reporting  
rules and procedures.

Your Business Reality Ltd strictly protects the security of your personal  
information and honours your choices for its intended use. We  
carefully protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access  
or disclosure, alteration, or destruction.

Your personal  
information is never shared outside the company without your  
permission, except under conditions explained above. Inside the  
company, data is stored in password-controlled servers with limited  
access. Your information may be stored and processed in the USA or  
any other country where Your Business Reality Ltd, its subsidiaries, affiliates or  
agents are located.

You also have a significant role in protecting your information. No  
one can share these see or edit your personal information without  
knowing your user name and password, so do not with others.

**NOTICE CONCERNING CHILDREN AND TO PARENTS**

We adhere to the Children’s Privacy Act. You must be 18 years of age  
to join or use hostdatsite.com or any of the recommended or linked sites.  
This site follows the guidelines, policies and laws of the Federal  
Trade Commission (www.ftc.gov). We retain the right to refuse anyone  
membership in any of our sites. If we learn or have reason to  
believe that a User is underage according to the guidelines,  
policies and laws of the Federal Trade Commission, we will promptly  
revoke that User’s account and delete any personal information.

**ENFORCEMENT**

 ****

****If for some reason you believe Your Business Reality Ltd has not adhered to  
these principles, please notify us at: http://benjaminobiamiwe.com/helpdesk/view.php or by  
certified mail, return receipt requested, to Your Business Reality Ltd, 11 Murray Street, London. NW19RE. We  
will do our best to determine and correct the problem promptly. Be  
certain the words Privacy Policy are in the Subject line.

**ELECTRONIC PRODUCT REGISTRATION**

When you buy and install a new product, we may ask you to register  
your purchase electronically. When you do, we merge your  
registration information with any information you’ve already left  
with us (we call that information your personal profile). If you  
haven’t previously registered with us, we create a personal profile  
for you from your product registration information. If you ever want  
to review or update that information, you can click on Update  
Profile, and edit any of the Personal Information in your profile.  
If you haven’t already created a membership, we will ask you to do  
so. This ensures that only you can access your information.

**CUSTOMER OR MEMBERSHIP PROFILES**

As mentioned above, every registered customer or member has a unique  
personal profile. Each profile is assigned a unique personal  
identification username, which helps us ensure that only you can  
access your profile.

When you register,  
you create your profile, your username and password. It is your  
passport to seamless travel across your member area, allowing you to  
download software and order more plug-in modules without having to  
fill out registration forms with information you’ve already  
provided. Even if you switch computers, you won’t have to  
re-register – just use your Registration ID to identify yourself.

**WHAT WE DO WITH  
THE INFORMATION YOU SHARE**

When you join us, you provide us with your contact information,  
including your name and email address. We use this information to  
send you updates about your order, questionnaires to measure your  
satisfaction with our service and announcements about new and  
exciting services that we offer. When you order from us, our 3rd  
party payment processors such as PayPal and 2checkout.com will ask  
for your credit card number and billing address. They use this  
information only to bill you for the product(s) you order at that  
time.

We occasionally hire  
other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, including  
programming, answering Customer/Member questions about products or  
services, sending email and processing event registration. We will  
only provide those companies the information they need to deliver  
the service, and they are prohibited from using that information for  
any other purpose.

**CONFIDENTIALITY AND SECURITY OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**

Except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy, Your Business Reality Ltd  
will not share your personal information with any third parties  
without your consent.

Your Business Reality Ltd will disclose your personal information, without notice,  
only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that  
such action is necessary to:

i. Conform to the  
edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Your Business Reality Ltd  
or the site;

ii. Protect and defend the rights or property of Your Business Reality Ltd and its  
family of Websites;

iii. Enforce our Terms of Use Agreement [insert hyperlink here]; or

iv. Act under exigent circumstances to protect the safety of the  
public or users of the Site.

If your information is lost or stolen, you must promptly notify us  
if your credit card, user name, or password is lost, stolen, or used  
without permission. In such an event, we will remove that credit  
card number, user name, or password from your account and update our  
records accordingly.

The Site contains links to other websites. We are not responsible  
for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. We also  
make email services, bulletin board services, chat areas, news  
groups, forums, communities, personal web pages, calendars, photo  
albums, file cabinets and/or other message or communication  
facilities designed to enable User to communicate with others (each  
a “Communication Service” and collectively “Communication Services”)  
available to you. Please understand that any information that is  
disclosed in these areas becomes public information. We have no  
control over its use and you should exercise caution when deciding  
to disclose your Personal Information.

**PERSONAL  
INFORMATION-WHY AND HOW “IP ADDRESSES” ARE USED**

An IP address is a basic element of the way the Internet functions.  
It is a number that identifies your computer according to its IP  
address, and IP numbers are assigned to web sites automatically. IP  
addresses may also be identified in “header” information on emails.  
There may also be other services and occasions when IP addresses  
will appear. Always look carefully at what information may be  
displayed about you, including your IP address, and if you are  
unsure or uncomfortable about the appearance of your IP address, do  
not use that service.

In addition to being an important part of how computers communicate  
with each other correctly, IP addresses can be used for other  
things, as well. In Your Business Reality Ltd’s case, IP addresses are collected  
for smooth operation in administrating our Web Site system, for  
purposes of collecting the non-personal “grouping” information for  
use by Your Business Reality Ltd and certain third parties, as discussed above,  
and to generally monitor the use of hostdatsite.com. IP addresses are  
exchanged many times when you are surfing the web, so, for example,  
if you select a web page or link within Your Business Reality Ltd, the IP address  
is recorded by the server by which Your Business Reality Ltd’s Web Site is  
connected to the internet.

For most purposes, your IP address will not be connected with  
personally identifying information, only the fact of that access to  
a given place on our web sites gets noted, but who you are  
individually will be anonymous, even to Your Business Reality Ltd.  However,  
as with certain information discussed in other parts of this  
document, IP Address information will be used to help us identify a  
person if Your Business Reality Ltd, in good faith, believes it important for  
ensuring proper compliance with our rules and policies, if it  
appears to be necessary to comply with laws and to protect  
Your Business Reality Ltd, our members and customers or other third parties.

**PERSONAL  
INFORMATION-OPTING OUT**

Your Business Reality Ltd, our affiliates or selected third parties may use  
personal information you give Your Business Reality Ltd for marketing and  
promotions. You do not have to let us use this information in that  
manner. This is called “opting out,” and it means you can tell us  
not to use your personal information for these purposes:

i. Listing you in any  
Customer/Member directory,

ii. Receiving information from us about Your Business Reality Ltd and our services  
and products, or

iii. Receiving information from third parties selected by us  
because, for example, your interests seem to match services or  
products they offer. To opt out, contact http://benjaminobiamiwe.com/helpdesk/view.php, modify  
your personal information or cancel your Membership.

In addition, there may be specific opt-out processes available when  
you enter certain areas of our Web Site, join groups, use services  
or when other merchandise is offered. When you see such opt-out  
notices, read them for information on how to opt out at that time.  
Also, some promotions may ask if you’d like additional information.  
Choosing to ask for additional information may require transfer of  
your email address, but if more personal information than that is  
required, you will be notified prior to such information being  
transmitted and may opt out by cancelling the request at that time.

**OTHER IMPORTANT  
COMPANY PRIVACY ISSUES**

A “Cookie” is a small file sent to and stored in your computer to  
keep accurate records and customize certain services. In fact, it’s  
become so common that you can almost always expect cookies to be  
sent to your computer from a wide variety of Internet sites.

For Your Business Reality Ltd,  
cookies are designed to try to make your visits more personal and  
helpful according to the ways you use our Web Sites. They tell us  
the name that a Customer/Member uses at Your Business Reality Ltd and can tailor  
things like greetings, e-cards and so-forth to make your use of  
Your Business Reality Ltd feel like you’re right at home. They can also tell us,  
for example, that you focus on particular types of information you  
need as a Customer/Member, and the cookie may automatically see to  
it that when you log in you get a message about some new feature in  
your areas of interest or about other services that fit the way you  
use Your Business Reality Ltd. Also, sometimes when messages are sent to certain  
Your Business Reality Ltd destinations, like “customer service,” a cookie may be  
used to help process your message more efficiently and accurately.

However, cookies at  
Your Business Reality Ltd are never used for storing or accessing important  
personal information that you alone should control the use of-like  
your password or your credit card number.

Even though cookies  
are usually thought to be helpful to web sites and their users  
alike, not everybody wants them being put in their computer. That’s  
okay, but there are two things you need to know: if you don’t have  
cookies, not everything on your Your Business Reality Ltd visits may be  
accessible, as efficient or as personable; and, stopping cookies is  
something we can’t do, instead you have to do it in your own  
computer.

Stopping cookies  
shouldn’t be difficult; however, because cookies are so commonly  
used and welcomed today, most browsers are set to automatically  
accept them. Even so, if you look through the settings in your  
browser, often in “preferences,” “setup” or “configuration,” you  
should be able to find a place where you can change the cookies  
setting, either to tell your browser never to accept cookies, or to  
tell your browser to notify you if a cookie is about to be sent and  
give you a chance to accept it or not. In the latter case, you  
should know that cookies are often just numbered or use some kind of  
computer term that will not be helpful for you to identify what the  
cookie is actually for so that you can make a clear choice, but the  
option is yours.

**SPECIAL CONCERNS ABOUT HYPERLINKS**

In this document, there are buttons or underlined words and phrases  
that you can click on. You will find these all over our Web Site and  
nearly every other web site you visit throughout the Internet, too.  
Some of them link to other parts of the same web site, but others  
will send you to another site unrelated to the web site you were at.  
This kind of link is called a hyperlink and could send you to a web  
page a block away or on the other side of the world.

When we use  
hyperlinks at Your Business Reality Ltd, we try to make sure they are updated and  
accurate links and that they are compatible with the kinds of  
visitors we have. However, Your Business Reality Ltd has no control over the  
business, operations or representations of these hyperlinks to  
unrelated web sites-and any hyperlinks included on them-and what the  
destination web pages may contain. Your Business Reality Ltd’s Privacy Policy does  
not cover other such destinations. You should always be careful at  
other web sites about how they operate and how information is being  
used. They may have their own policies that differ from  
Your Business Reality Ltd’s, they may send different kinds of cookies and they may  
gather and use information in very different ways than Your Business Reality Ltd.

We can take no  
responsibility or protect you on other web sites, so always be  
careful-not just about things like opting out on advertising, but  
also about safety and security. Once again, carefully protect  
personal information about yourself, and be wary of who might get  
such information, especially the public through chat-rooms, bulletin  
boards or by email. Not being careful about this can be risky, and  
because Your Business Reality Ltd can’t control these hyperlinked sites or users,  
and because our own policies and rules don’t apply, the risk is on  
you to decide how, and how not, to use them.

**DO YOU ACCEPT OUR  
PRIVACY POLICY? **

By using this Web Site, you are verifying that you agree to, and  
will abide by, the terms of the Your Business Reality Ltd Privacy Policy.  

IF YOU DO NOT AGREE  
TO DO SO, STOP VISITING OUR WEB SITES.

Second, check our  
privacy policy every once in a while. Certain things may change over  
time, and we may include new information and privacy policies that  
will be placed in this document. If you continue to visit  
Your Business Reality Ltd after any such changes, you will again be verifying that  
you agree to, and will abide by, the current privacy policy, as it  
then exists.

**UPDATES AND  
CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY**

We reserve the right, at any time and without notice, to add to,  
change, update, or modify this Privacy Policy, simply by posting  
such change, update, or modification on the Site and without any  
other notice to you. Any such change, update, or modification will  
be effective immediately upon posting on the Site.

**QUESTIONS &  
COMMENTS?**

Your Business Reality Ltd is always ready to review your questions and comments  
and we will attempt to give you our best responses. Remember, we  
have a lot of Customer/Member s and other visitors to respond to, as  
well, but we will try to reply as promptly and thoroughly as  
possible. To contact Your Business Reality Ltd about our privacy policy, send an  
email to http://benjaminobiamiwe.com/helpdesk/view.php.

* * *

It Is Protected Under Copyright. Do Not Copy Or Replicate Without A Valid  
Licence.
